Her throat's been cut.
Victim is
Navy Ensign Janine Wilt.
Ensign Wilt gained
remote access from this laptop
to a home computer.
Linked to a chat room?
What were they talking about?
Asking if I was lonely
and did I know my calling?
So you turned to Ensign Wilt.
She knew computers,
blocked the chat room
and everyone on it.
Do you know any of them?
Hellbent427.
Hellbent427 is Bradley Simek.
Nobody move!
Don't.
No!
NCIS Cyber linked
Bradley Simek's communications
to a specific terror cell:
The Calling.
The Calling is making a strong
push to recruit children.
We've sent you background
on a Calling leader in France.
His name is Matthew Rousseau.
Several Calling loyalists
are seeking S-mines
on the black market.
Interpol is assembling
a think tank.
I would like you
to represent NCIS.
SS_Builder-48.
The SS stands for Sadiq Samar.
Luke Harris-- Wendy and
David Harris reported him
TONY: Luke Harris-- Wendy and
missing last night.
They are his adoptive parents.
Mom! Mom!
Dad! No!
Duck, I got to reach this kid.
I know nothing
about any S-mines.
Samar could be trying
to connect the mines.
Dorneget, listen to me,
there's a threat to the hotel.
They know you're there. You need
to get everyone out of there.
Everybody out! Go, go!
Gibbs. Dorneget didn't make it.
BISHOP:
Gibbs. CIA officer
Joanna Teague.
VANCE: Gibbs. CIA officer
Agent Dorneget's mother.
Officer Teague.
My son is dead and his killers
are still out there.
I'd say we've got
some work to do.
(crossing bell clanging,
train horn blowing in distance)
♪ ♪
(coughs, sputters)
소년은 어딨나, Sadiq?
Where's the boy, Sadiq?
(grunts)
이러지 마
Come on, now.
Don't do this.
이 총으로 쏴 버릴 수도 있어
I know the taser
stings a little,
내가 아무 선택도 할 수 없게 남겨두지 마
but you left me no choice.
넌 누구야?
Who are you?
매우 화난 한 엄마지
A very angry mother
with a short fuse.
소년은 어딨어?
Where's the boy?
당신이 무슨 말을 하는지 난 모르겠어
I don't know
what you're talking about.
맹세해
난 아무것도 몰라
I swear.
I know nothing.
아무것도 아닌게 충분할 수 있지
Nothing might be
stretching it.
온라인에서 아이들은 널 믿었어 Sadiq
Online, these kids
trust you, Sadiq.
어리석게 굴지마
난 배고풀 때 널 물을 수 있어
Don't be stupid.
I only bite when I'm hungry.
Luke는 어디있어?
Where's Luke?
소년은 어디있어?
Where's the boy?
(gagging)
그들이 그를 데려갔어
They took him back.
Luke?
그래
(grunts) Yes.
(groaning)
어디로 ?
Where?
이라크로
(tea kettle whistling)
To Iraq.
Zakho로
To Zakho.
(tea kettle continues whistling)
(music stops)
(coughing, panting)
(kettle's whistling subsides,
train passes by)
Gibbs
Gibbs.
그들이 Luke를 어디로 데려갔는지 알아냈어요
I know where they took Luke.
♪ NCIS 12x24 ♪
Neverland
Original Air Date on May 12, 2015
NCIS 12x24
Neverland
Original Air Date on May 12, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Mimmi's 1st substitle (의역/오역 많음, 피드백 환영)
@elder_man
♪ ♪
(36시간 전)
전 제 아들을 죽인 사람들을 알고 싶어요
I want the people
who killed my son.
저희도 그렇습니다
As do we.
Dorneget 요원은
우리 팀에 매우 중요한 멤버였어요
Special Agent Dorneget
was a valued
member of my team.
00:03:47,258 -> 00:03:49,225
그리고 난 남겨진 유일한 가족이죠
And the only family I had left.
당신이 이해하는지 잘 모르겠어요
I'm not sure you understand.
저는 이 사건을 제가 조사하기를 요청했어요
I'm asking to be
read in on the case.
이미 제 상관에게 말했습니다
I've already
spoken with my superiors.
Teague 요원
Joanna입니다
Officer Teague...
Joanna.
개인적으로 사건과 관계하는건
당신에게 좋은 생각이라고 생각하지 않아요
I don't think
it's a good idea for you
to be personally involved.
00:04:06,010 -> 00:04:07,877
Gibbs, 전 IOC입니다.
Gibbs, I'm IOC.
전 계속 중동 사이버 군사행동과
관련해 일해왔어요
I consistently work
in Middle Eastern cyber ops.
이건 제 전문분야에요
This is my area of expertise.
당신과 Dorneget요원과의 개인적 관계는
NCIS 내부에 안 알려져 있습니다
VANCE: Your personal
connection to Agent Dorneget
was unknown inside NCIS.
00:04:18,389 -> 00:04:21,057
현재 있는 사람들을 제외하곤요
Present company
excluded.
당신 아드님의 요청이었습니다
Per your son's request.
Ned는 그 누구도, 자신이 정부와
관련된 집안이라는 걸 알길 원치 않았습니다
Ned didn't want anyone to know
about his government pedigree.
그는 그의 동료가 존중받기를 원했습니다
He wanted the respect
of his coworkers,
그는 훌륭한 요원이었구요
that he was a good agent.
그리고 그는 더럽게 좋은 사람이었구요
And he was a damn good one.
(sighs heavily)
매우 Ned 같군요
Well, that was very Ned.
그는 자신이 어디서 왔는지
사람들이 알길 원하지 않았어요
He didn't want people
to know what he came from.
그의 유년기는 평탄하지 못했어요
He had a rough childhood.
His father was a cop
그의 아빠는 업무 중에 사람을 죽였죠, 그리고
who was killed
in the line of duty, and...
나는 내 CIA 경력을 쫓으며
간신히 그 옆에 있었죠
I was barely around,
chasing my CIA career.
그의 할머니에게 감사해야겠죠
그녀가 그를 키웠어요
Thank God for his grandmother.
She raised him.
Ned는 당신에 대해 많이 얘기했어요
Gibbs 요원님
Ned talked
about you a lot,
Agent Gibbs.
00:05:00,431 -> 00:05:03,366
당신의 리더십, 규칙
Your leadership, your rules...
그는 규칙 1번에 대해 얘기했을 겁니다
He talk about rule number ten:
절대 개인적인 사건에 관계하지 마라
Never get personally
involved in a case?
당신은 부모였어요
You were a parent.
아이를 잃었구요
You lost a child.
당신은 이해해야만 해요
You should understand.
난 이게 필요해요
I need this.
그리고 Ned도 그럴 자격이 있구요
(sniffles)
And Ned deserves it.
부탁드려요
Please.
Tony 아직 투시력이 아직 작동안해요?
That X-ray vision
working yet, there, Tony?
No.
응
만약 Steve Jobs가 살아있었다면
If Steve Jobs were still alive
우리는 투시력을 지금 사용할 수 있을꺼야
그렇지?
we'd have X-ray vision
by now, wouldn't we?
Steve Jobs가 그리워
I miss Steve Jobs.
그건 그렇고
계속 하자
All right.
Where are we?
'Calling'의 지배 구조를
이해하려고 노력해봤어요
Trying to understand
the power structure
of The Calling.
00:05:45,476 -> 00:05:47,843
우리는 Sadiq Samar가 아직 밖에 있는걸 알아요
We know Sadiq Samar
is still out there,
그리고 그가 Ensign Wilt해군을 죽인것도요
and that he murdered
Navy Ensign Wilt.
McGee가 Matthew Rousseau 심문한 후에
After after McGee interrogated
Matthew Rousseau,
그는 여기 인도되었고, 자백했어요
he was delivered here
'Calling'의 카이로에서의 역할은
and admitted
The Calling's role in Cairo.
법의학 적인 결과는?
Forensic results?
감사해요
Thanks.
이집트의 폭탄파편에서도 Sadiq Samar의
DNA가 발견되었어요
Touch DNA
ties Sadiq Samar
to the bomb fragments
in Egypt, too.
00:06:03,061 -> 00:06:04,460
그리고 우리는 이미 그가
아이들을 모으는
And we already know
채팅방의 책임자라는 것을 알고 있구요
he's in charge of chat room
recruitment, so we are dealing
컴퓨터 지식과 매력적인 엔지니어로써요
with a computer-savvy
and personable
mechanical engineer.
00:06:10,334 -> 00:06:11,334
그래
Yeah.
반드시 별도의 범주가 있어야해
There should be
a separate category
범죄 추구하는 사람들에겐
그렇지 않아?
for criminal overachievers,
don't you think?
만약 Sadiq과 Rousseau가 'Calling'의
대중적인 모습이라면
If Sadiq and Rousseau are the
public faces of The Calling,
그 윗사람은 누구일까요?
나도 모르지
then who's next level up?
I don't know.
이것은 국제테러행위의 모습이 아니야
This is not the face
of international terrorism.
선배가 놀란것 같군요
You'd be surprised.
Tim, 우리 사무실로 돌아와서 반가워
It's nice to have you back
in the big orange room, Tim.
00:06:29,120 -> 00:06:31,120
저도 돌아와서 반가워요
Nice to be back.
다만 Dorneget도 우리와 있으면 좋을텐데
I just wish Dorneget
was here with us.
Teague 요원님.
저는 Ellie Bishop 입니다
Officer Teague.
I'm Ellie Bishop.
애도를 표합니다
You have my deepest
sympathies.
감사해요 Bishop 요원
Thank you, Agent Bishop.
제 생각엔 당신이 Tim이군요
And I'm guessing you're Tim.
네 그렇습니다
Yes, ma'am.
Ned는 당신을 매우 많이 좋아했어요
Ned liked you very, very much.
저는 이집트에서 그의 곁에 머물러야 했어요
I should have stayed
with him in Egypt.
그가 저를 필요로 할때
옆에 있었어야 했어요
I should have been there
when he needed me.
당신은 당신의 일을 한 거에요
You did your job.
You all did.
그런 질문 말아요
Don't ever question that.
당신이 DiNozzo군요
You must be DiNozzo.
애도를 표합니다
My condolences.
Ned는 훌륭했다고 생각해요
I really thought
Ned was great.
그는 정말로
당신과 당신 아버지의 관계를 존경했어요
He really admired your
relationship with your father.
아
Ah... (soft laugh) yeah.
아버지는 특별하시죠
Well, Dad is special.
네 Gibbs입니다
Yes, Gibbs.
네 Duck?
Yeah, Duck?
네 그녀를 데리고 갈께요
Yeah, sure, I'll bring her down.
갈 준비 되셨나요?
Ready to go?
네
Yes.
Teague 요원, 당신에게 경고해야만 해요
DUCKY:
Officer Teague, I must warn you
소이탄의 파편은 대단히 파괴적이었어요
the shrapnel
from the incendiary device
was devastating.
00:07:35,086 -> 00:07:37,553
박사님, 그는 제 아들이에요
He's my son, Doctor.
아들이 보고 싶네요
(voice breaking):
I want to see him.
Palmer군
Mr. Palmer.
얘야 나는 네가 정말 자랑스럽단다
I'm so proud of you, baby.
편히 자거라
Sleep now.
신참, 얼마나 더 남았나?
FRANKS:
How many more, probie?
몇 번이나 더 이런 춤을 춰야하지?
How many times
we gonna do this dance?
요원들은 네가 주시할 때 죽지 않아
Agents can't keep dying
on your watch.
저는 Gibbs요원도 허락할거라고 생각해요
TEAGUE: I'm sure agent Gibbs would
grant me the courtesy.
Jethro
Jethro, Officer Teague
Teague요원께서 이 파편을 자세히 보길 원하네
would like to take
a close look at the shrapnel.
전
I would prefer...
We can learn a lot from
제 경험상 그 금속조각들에서
많은것들을 알 수 있어요
every piece of metal,
and in my experience...
전 제 공식적인 부검이 끝날 때까지
기다리셨으면 좋겠습니다
I would prefer to wait until
I've begun my formal autopsy.
Duck... 빼주세요
Duck... pull it out,
그녀에게 보여주세요
show it to her.
Teague요원
JIMMY:
Officer Teague,
저는 시신을 실제로 옮기는 데 있진 않았지만
I know I wasn't at
the actual transfer.
저는 소아과 의사였습니다
You see, I-I was at
the pediatrician's.
제, 제 딸이 숨을 쌕쌕 쉬죠
See, my-my daughter
has a little wheeze
며칠밤동안 그녀가 낫기를 노력했어요
and-and we've
actually been trying
to steam it out of her
for a few nights...
00:08:51,829 -> 00:08:53,062
Palmer군
Mr. Palmer.
정말 죄송합니다
저는 단지 이 말을 반복하고 싶었어요
I'm sorry.
I just want to reiterate
우리는 모두 Ned를 죽인 범인을
잡기위해 모였다는 것을요
that we are all in this
00:08:58,836 -> 00:09:01,103
그게 무엇이든지라도요
to catch Ned's killers.
No matter what.
감사해요
Thank you.
자네의 포인트는 타당했네
Your point is well-taken.
Now could you give me
이제 거기 있는 작은 박스를 하나 주지 않겠나?
one of those
small containers, please.
티타늄이군
That's titanium.
Abby가 말하길 Sadiq가
폭발물을 수정했다고 했어요
Abby said Sadiq
modified the explosives.
보아하니 규칙적인 파편은
Apparently regular
shrapnel wasn't
사람을 죽이기에 충분하지 않았나 보네요
deadly enough for his taste.
아마 이것을 추적할 수 있을꺼에요
We might be able to track it.
지역 폭탄가게에서
티타늄 볼 베어링만 단순히 사진 않았겠죠
You don't just buy
titanium ball bearings
at the local bomb store.
00:09:29,533 -> 00:09:33,402
세계 최대의 티타늄 공급업체는 러시아라네
The world's largest supplier
of titanium is Russia.
시작하기 좋은 장소네요
Good place to start.
Run down the source,
수입업자를 추적해 살인범을 찾겠어요
track the importer,
find the killer.
Gibbs, 저는 아직 몇명의
러시아 정보원을 갖고 있어요
I still have a few Russian
connections left, Gibbs.
당신은요?
You?
나도 한 사람을 알고 있네
Yeah, I know a guy.
다른건 없나?
Anything?
카이로의 호텔보안 업체와 얘기해 봤습니다
I spoke to hotel
security in Cairo.
그들은 20대 중반의 금발 남자가
They reported seeing
a blond-haired man, mid-20s,
폭발직전 입구 옆에 서있는 것을 봤다고합니다
standing in the entrance
just before the explosion.
이게 호텔 보안 카메라로부터
얻은 영상입니다
McGEE: These are screen grabs from
the hotel security camera.
다른 신원관련 사항은?
아직 없습니다
Any I.D.?
Not yet.
Sadiq에 대해서는?
What about Sadiq?
그 장소에서 두 명의 목격자를 찾았어요
Well, we have two
eyewitnesses that place
Sadiq Samar는 한달전
같은 카이로 호텔에 머물렀습니다
Sadiq Samar in the same
Cairo hotel a month ago.
정찰중이었군
Doing recon.
Then Homeland picked up
그리고 크루즈를 이용해
his trail using an alias
on a cruise ship
버지니아로 이동해왔습니다
that landed him
here in Virginia.
단지 제시간에 죽이는 역할이었군
Just in time to kill the ensign.
Bishop, 그를 찾아내
Mm.
Bishop, track him down.
헤이
Guys,
러시안 친구로부터 들은 말이
I heard from our
Russian friend.
오 Pavlenko는 잘 지낸데요?
Oh, how is comrade Pavlenko?
Slippery as ever?
그는 내 아들을 죽인 티타늄 조각이
He thinks the titanium
that killed my son
지역의 항공우주와 관련있는
was imported by a local
aerospace company,
Bianca Aviation라는
회사에서 수입됐다고 생각해
Bianca Aviation.
Roger Dietz의 이름으로 사인된
Purchased by a
dummy corporation.
유령회사를 찾아가봐
Signed for by Roger Dietz.
Roger Dietz의 베어링 회사로 가보겠습니다 boss.
Getting our bearings
on Roger Dietz, boss.
(music playing,
muffled through earbuds)
Luke, 어떻게 잘 견디고 있니?
How you holding up, Luke?
나는 가식적으로 행동하지 않을꺼야
난 안단다
I won't pretend
I know.
그래서
So...
제게 무슨 일이 일어난거죠?
What happens to me now,
Gibbs 요원님?
Agent Gibbs?
너는 안전하단다
Once you're safe,
너는 가족도 있고
you have family.
우리는 너를 친척에게 데려다 줄꺼야
We'll reach out
to your relatives.
그들은 저를 중동지역의
입양된 아이로만 여길꺼에요
They're just lining up
to take in the...
Middle Eastern adopted kid.
00:11:30,201 -> 00:11:33,736
너가 어디서 왔는지는 중요하지 않단다
Luke 가족은 가족이야
Doesn't matter where you're
from, Luke-- family's family.
사람들이 저 때문에 죽었어요
People are dead
because of me.
넌 아무도 죽이지 않았단다
You didn't kill anybody.
너는 지금부터 돕도록 시도해야해
You're trying to help now.
그건 중요해
That counts for something.
한 요원님이 죽었어요
An agent died.
그래
Yeah.
그리고 'Calling'은 책임이 있어요
And The Calling is responsible.
내가 당신에게
보여줄 수 있다면 어떻게 될까요 ?
What if...
I could show you...
00:12:00,932 -> 00:12:05,234
정확히 제 부모님을 죽인 사람들을요
exactly who killed my parents?
Safari Sandy를 만났어요
Meet Safari Sandy.
Safari Sandy는 기린이군
Safari Sandy's a giraffe.
버트의 먼 사촌이자
Yes. A distant relative of Bert
Harrises의 편집증 결과
the Hippo and a direct result
of the Harrises' paranoia
청소부를 도벽이 있다고 생각했기 때문에
regarding a certain
sticky-fingered cleaning lady.
카메라가 있었군.
Nanny cam.
네 맞아요
Yep. Exactly.
그래서 불행히도
Safari Sandy의 눈이 제거됐어요
Hence Safari Sandy's
unfortunate exenteration.
Eyeball removal.
00:12:28,759 -> 00:12:30,859
범죄현장에서 기린을 본 적이 없어
I did not see a giraffe
at the crime scene.
그게 포인트에요
That's the point.
Safari Sandy는 포식을 한 동물이에요
Safari Sandy
is a stuffed animal,
그래서 확실히 위협적이지 않죠
so is decidedly nonthreatening
많이 먹은 상태에서는요
in her stuffed-ness.
이 카메라는 모션센서를 갖고 있어요
The camera has
a motion sensor.
그래서 움직임이 있을 때 기록을 시작하죠
So whenever there's movement,
it starts recording,
그리고 그 파일은 내부 SD card로 전송돼요
and then the files are sent
to an internal SD card.
잘했어!
Yeah. Good. Put it up.
Gibbs, 그 카메라에는 모션센서는
Gibbs, the camera's
motion sensors
밤에 무언가를 녹화했을지도 몰라요
caught something that night.
Harrises의 살인과 관계된것과요
The Harrises' murder.
카메라는 모든것을 기록하니까요
The camera
recorded everything,
살해범의 정체를 포함해서요
including the identity
of the killer.
Abbs 재생해봐, 얼른!
Play it, Abbs. Go.
누구세요?
MRS. HARRIS (gasps):
Who are you?
이봐!
남의 집에서 뭘 하는거야?
MR. HARRIS: Hey! Hey!
What are you doing in our house?
넌 이럴 필요..
총 내려놔
You don't have to--
put the gun down.
총 내려놔, 안돼!
총 내려..
Put the gun down-- no!
Put it...
오 신이시여!
-(gunfire)
-MRS. HARRIS: Oh, my God!
안돼!
(sobbing):
No!
(Mrs. Harris sobbing, gasping)
(gunshot)
(shuddering sigh)
오 죄송해요
Oh. Sorry.
이곳에 누군가 계신지 몰랐어요
I didn't know
someone was in here.
괜찮단다
No, it's okay.
숙제를 테이블에 놔두고 와서요
I, um, left my
homework on the table.
이것만 가져갈께요
I just need to
get it. I'll...
네가 Luke구나
You must be Luke.
누군가요?
Who's that?
내 아들이란다
That's my son.
그는 이곳에서 일했지, 그런데
He worked here, but, uh...
이제 그는 갔단다
he's gone now.
그 돌아가신 요원님이군요
The agent who was killed.
그의 이름이 뭔가요?
What was his name?
Ned
Ned.
너도 알겠지만
You know,
너는 그의 어렸을 때를 떠올리게 한단다
you kind of remind me of him
a little bit.
요원들은 내게 정확히 무슨일이 있었는지
얘기해 주지 않고 있어
Look, the-the agents won't tell
me what happened exactly, and...
그래서 난 많이 궁금하단다
I have so many questions.
다 제 잘못이에요
It's kind of my fault.
저희 부모님
My parents, uh,
당신의 아들, 그들은 모두 죽었어요
your son...
그리고 난 그것을 멈추기 위해
아무것도 하지 않았어요
they're all gone now, and
I didn't do anything to stop it.
Luke 네가 그들을 죽인게 아니란다
You didn't kill them, Luke.
알아요. 근데
I know, but I...
가는게 낫겠어요
Look, I better go.
Luke
Luke...
Luke 제발
Luke, please.
너의 친구에 대해 말해주렴
Tell me about your friends.
그들은 제 친구가 아니에요
They're not my friends.
그러면 그들을 찾는 방법을 내게 말해주렴
Then tell me how to find them.
티타늄은 가볍기 때문에 선호되죠
Titanium is generally preferred
because it's lightweight
그리고 고온/고압도 견딜 수 있구요
and can withstand high
compression and temperature.
정밀검사가 끝났어요
Uh, the precision finish
균일한 표면을 확인하기 위해서죠
패인곳이 없네요
ensures surface uniformity.
No pits.
패인걸 원치 않는군요
Don't want pits.
우리는 주로 이것을 항공기 랜딩기어에 사용합니다
We mostly use these
in aircraft landing gear.
저는 많은 양을 주문했구요
그래서 저희가 여기 있는 겁니다.
I order 'em by the bushel.
That's why we're here.
당신의 주문량 중의 하나가 카이로에서 끝났어요
One of your bushels ended up
in Cairo, Egypt.
뭐라고요?
How's that, now?
당신은 P.O.에 서명했어요
BISHOP:
Well, you signed the P.O.
이 장치에 사용되는 베어링을 위해서
for the bearings used
in these devices.
장치는 카이로에서 이 폭탄에 사용되었구요
TONY: Devices used in this
bombing in Cairo, Egypt.
아니에요
전 그런것을 하지 않았어요
No, ma'am.
I-I did no such thing.
당신이 인정한 물류관리 대장은
가짜 경찰에 팔렸어요
The inventory you just admitted
to controlling was sold
to a dummy corp
00:15:46,023 -> 00:15:47,656
Sadiq Samar에게요
fronting
Sadiq Samar,
폭탄을 터뜨린 테러리스트죠
the terrorist responsible
for the bombing.
오 신이시여
Oh, God.
저는
I, uh...
저는 아무것도 몰라요
I don't know anything
아무것도
about any, uh...
우리의 물품목록은 조심스럽게 관리되고 있어요
All our inventory
is carefully accounted for.
명백하군
Clearly.
그럼 당신의 개인 계좌에서 무언가를 찾는다면
So will we find anything
when we go
through your personal accounts?
00:16:05,342 -> 00:16:07,376
당신은 새로운 곳에 넣어두지 않았어요 그렇죠?
TONY: You didn't just put
in a new pool, did you?
가족을 위해선가요 Roger씨?
당신은 신장모양의 사내같군요
For the fam, Roger? You seem
like a kidney-shaped guy to me.
당신들은 아무것도 찾지 못할 겁니다
You won't find anything.
Are you calling my bluff, Roger?
큰 양동이를 가져와야겠어요
Because that would take
big brass ones.
러시아에서 만들어진 티타늄 볼 베어링이네
GIBBS: Titanium ball bearings made
in Russia.
Bianca Aviation의 사내가 비밀리에 팔았지
Sold,
under the table,
by a guy at Bianca Aviation
00:16:30,267 -> 00:16:33,101
이 자에게
to this clown.
이 자를 아나?
You know him?
그는 좋은 사람들을 죽였어
He killed some good people.
해군 Ensign Wilt.
Navy Ensign Wilt.
Luke Harris의 부모
Luke Harris's parents.
우리가 그가 이집트 폭탄과 관련시키더라도
Hell, we even linked him
to the bombing in Egypt.
너도 알겠지만 이건 잠깐이야
You know,
we've been at this a while.
난 서두를 것 없어
I'm in no rush.
난 네가 시간이 부족한걸 알고 있지
And I know you are made of time.
Luke는 삐뚫어진 아이였어요
Luke is a...
misguided young man.
가엽게도
Pity.
그는 그의 길을 찾을꺼에요
He'll find his way.
음
Mmm.
아마도
Maybe.
이 자가 누군지 말해
Tell me who this is.
몰라요
Don't know.
살면서 이 자를 본 적이 없어요
Never seen him before
in my life.
어디서 그를 찾을 수 있지?
Where would I find him?
오른쪽으로 두 번째, 그런 다음 아침까지 쭉
* 피터팬의 네버랜에 가는 방법 *
Second star to the right
and straight on till morning.
왜 아이들을 이용하지?
Why use kids?
왜 물고기가 헤엄을 치죠?
Why do fish swim?
같은 이유죠
For the same reason
disenfranchised children
권리를 박탈당한 아이들이 자라서
그들의 목적을 찾죠
will rise up
to find their purpose.
그들은 반드시
They simply must.
필연적인 거에요
It is inevitable.
그의 말을 들어
FRANKS:
Listen to him,
얘기를 돌려
talkin' in circles.
그는 쓰레기야
He's scum.
사람들이 죽어가고 있어
좋은 사람들이
People are dying. Good people.
너의 사람들이
그리고 이건 매우 웃기지
Your people. And this
one thinks it's funny.
능글맞게 웃는 저 모습을 봐
Look at that smirk.
그를 부숴버려
Break him.
어서
Do it.
이름,
One name.
이름
이 자가 누구지?
Who is he?
이 동부시간은 나를 피해가네요
These Western time zones
elude me.
Arizona는 몇시죠?
What time is it in Arizona?
전 우리가 오후여행를 놓쳤다고 생각하는데요
I think
we've missed the afternoon tour.
(phone rings)
뭐라고, McGee?
What, McGee?
그랜드캐년의 남쪽 끝입니다 보스
McGEE: South rim
of the Grand Canyon, boss.
두 개 이상의 지뢰에요
뉴스에 나오고 있어요
Two more Bouncing Bettys.
It's all over the news.
국립공원관리청은 국토안보부 및 FBI와 함께
NEWSCASTER: The National Park
Service is working
with Homeland Security
and the FBI
누구에게 책임이 있는지 밝혀내려고 하고 있습니다
to determine who was responsible
00:19:01,902 -> 00:19:04,436
그랜드 캐년에 한 폭격에 대해서
for today's deadly attack
at the Grand Canyon.
더이상 자세한 내용은 없습니다
No further details
have been released.
충분하군
That's enough.
왜 국립공원이지 ?
Why in a national park?
왜 인적이 끊긴 곳이지?
Why in the middle of nowhere?
지뢰가 확인됐어요
Okay, Bouncing Bettys
are confirmed.
공원 관리인 한 명이 죽었구요
One park ranger dead,
3명의 등산객이 부상입었습니다.
three hikers wounded.
But five minutes later,
그러나 5분 후 투어버스들이
짐을 내릴 거래요
two tour buses
would have unloaded
지뢰가 터진 곳에서.
right where the bombs went off.
우리의 친구 Bianca Aviation가
Sadiq의 휴대폰 번호를 갖고 있었습니다
Our friend at Bianca Aviation
had a cell number for Sadiq
in his phone records.
00:19:26,794 -> 00:19:28,760
추적했나?
You track it?
Burn phone was found
Maryland에서 타버린 기계만 발견되었어요
Mount Roosevelt 캠퍼스 근처에서요
in a Dumpster in Maryland,
near the Mount Roosevelt campus.
말이 되는군
Makes sense.
20명의 엔지니어가
A bright 20-something engineer
대학 캠퍼스에 숨어 있었군
hiding in plain sight
on a college campus.
Cell의 배터리는 아직 작동중입니다
BISHOP: Cell's battery
was still working.
그는 아마 최근에 넘겼을꺼에요
가서 그를 찾아
He probably tossed it recently.
Go. Find him.
McGee.
Boss, 무언가를 찾아냈어요
Boss, I-I found something
Dorney는 절대 완수할 기회를 얻지 못했군요
that Dorney never got the-the
chance to follow through on.
온라인으로 모집된 아이들 전부에게
같은 노래가 발송되었어요
All the kids that were recruited
online were sent
the same group of songs.
00:19:54,855 -> 00:19:56,621
댄스클럽 음악이군
(music playing)
Dance club music.
이건 구체적으로 말하면 테크노에요
It's, uh, techno-industrial,
그런데
to be specific.
But, uh,
어디서 발송된건지 정확히 모르겠어요
I don't know exactly
where they come from.
그래서 찾고 있구요
I'm still digging.
부탁이네, McGee,
Do us a favor, McGee,
헤드폰을 끼게
dig with headphones.
Luke는 MP3 플레이어를 갖고 있어요 맞죠?
Luke carries an MP3 player,
right?
그래
Yeah.
난 그냥 말한거에요, Gibbs
I'm just saying, Gibbs,
아침에 그가 이런 음악을 들었는지
한 번 확인해 봐요
in the morning, let's see if
he has any songs like these.
이건 무언가를 의미할 수있어요.
It could mean
something.
음 그녀와 친해보이는군요
Well, she seemed friendly.
다른건요?
그녀의 이름은 Amber야
Anything?
Uh, her name is Amber.
응용 범죄학을 전공하고 있어
She's a criminal justice major,
그녀에게 아빠와 문제가 있고,
she has daddy issues,
그녀는 내 가택 수색 압류 기술에
대해 토론하고 싶어해
and she wanted to discuss my
search-and-seizure techniques.
그녀는 못할 꺼에요
(laughing):
She did not.
다 지어냈군요
아니야
You made all that up.
No.
안했어
I did not.
어쨋든 그녀는 Sadiq를 보지 못했데
Anyway, she hasn't
seen Sadiq,
우리는 이 캠퍼스에서 24시간 대기하고 있어야 해
and we have been
to every 24-hour
이제 본부로 전화할 시간이라고 생각하는데
study hall on campus. So I think
it's time to call it a night.
잠시만요
Hang on a second.
저기 잠깐만
Hey. Excuse me. Hi.
혹시 몇살이니?
Sorry, but how old are you?
18살이요
Eighteen.
아니지
Mm. No, you're not.
너는, 음.. 165살?
You're, what, 16, tops?
여기서 뭐하는 거지?
오늘은 학교 가는 날이잖아
What are you doing here?
It's a school day.
친구를 찾아왔어요
Visiting a friend.
제 형이요
그는 이 대학에 다니거든요
Uh, my brother.
He-he goes to college here.
아하 형? 아니면 친구?
brother or friend?
Ah. So which is it, Doogie,
네 이름이 뭐니?
What's your name?
이 자를 본적이 있어?
You seen this guy?
애들은 참 빠르군
Kids are fast.
이봐!
TONY:
Hey!
(engine revving)
(tires screeching,
horn honking)
(panting)
음식 식겠다
Mmm. Food's getting cold, dude.
배 안고파요
I'm not hungry.
마음대로 하세요
GIBBS:
Suit yourself.
내가 나중에 무엇을 사용할 수 있을까요?
You know
what I could use later?
아이스크림
Ice cream.
Larry의 가게가 아직도 그 거리에 있나요?
Is Larry's still
on Connecticut Avenue?
물론이지
GIBBS:
Yeah.
이 도시에서 최고의 'rum raisin' 이지
Best rum raisin in town.
저는 민트칩이요
I'm partial to mint chip.
나를 구닥다리라고 불러요
Call me old-fashioned.
Luke 너는 어떠니?
How about you, Luke?
가장 좋아하는 아이스크림을 먹었니?
You got a favorite ice cream?
모르겠어요
I don't know.
아이스크림 향이라구?
FRANKS:
Ice cream flavors?!
신참, 나는 알았어
Probie, I get it.
너는 그 소년을 믿기를 원해
그는 좋은 아이였어
You want to trust the boy.
He was a good kid.
과거에 그랬다는 거지
Emphasis on was.
아무것도 더이상 그렇게 보이진 않아
Nothing's what
it seems anymore.
결백은 젊음과 립스틱과 함께 오진 않아
Innocence doesn't come
with youth or lipstick.
내가 니 나이였을 때
난 책을 읽곤 했단다
When I was your age,
we used to read books.
지금은 단지 여행할 때
오디오북을 들을 뿐이지만
Now, I just download audiobooks,
그냥 음악이에요
listen to 'em when I travel.
It's just music.
나도 음악을 듣는단다
Oh, I have songs, too.
Dylan, Stones...
Jay-Z.
이건 그런 종류의 음악이 아니에요
It's not that kind of music.
음, 한번 들어볼 수 있을까?
Well, can I listen?
(scoffs)
왜 우리가 여기서 이러고 있는 거죠?
Why are we even doing this?
그 아이를 애지중지하는 것을 멈춰
Stop coddling the boy.
그를 압박해
무엇을 기다리는 건가?
Press him.
What are you waiting for?
지금 요원님 집에 갈 수 있나요?
Can we go back
to your house now?
물론이지
Yeah, sure.
그는 당신을 갖고 놀고 있어요, Gibbs,
He's playing you, Gibbs,
그리고 당신은 그를 놓아주고 있구요
and you're letting him.
적어도,
그녀는 규칙 36번을 잊지 않았구나
At least
she didn't forget rule 36.
Sadiq? Sadiq 저에요
Sadiq? Sadiq, it's me.
(train horn blowing
in distance)
낮에 왔구나
You came during the day.
내가 분명 밤에만 오라고 말했을텐데
I told you, you only
come here at night.
그들이 당신을 찾고 있어요
They're looking for you.
들어와
Get in.
Rousseau 짓이에요, 아니면 Luke거나
ELAN:
It must have been Rousseau.
그렇지 않으면 그들이 어떻게
여기까지 올 수 있어요?
Or Luke. How else would
they know where to look?
Luke와 있으면 도움되기 보다 위험하게 되었어요
Luke's become more of a danger
than a help,
그러나 여전히 그는 가치있지
but he still has value.
다른 사람들은 곧
이라크로 떠날꺼에요
The others are
leaving soon for Iraq.
우리 모두 같이 갈 수 있어요
We can all go together.
그들을 기다리게 하자
(train passing by)
Let 'em wait.
너는 Luke를 찾아,
그의 가족이 그를 필요로 한다고 확신시켜
You find Luke, convince him
his family needs him.
(door closes)
(industrial techno music plays
over headphones)
Abby?
헤이
Hey.
분자 54번에 오신 것을 환영합니다
Welcome to Molecule 54.
내 클럽이름이야
It's the name of my club.
자 이거 마셔, 아직 두 잔이 남아있어
And go for it-- there's
a two-drink minimum.
오
Oh.
고마워 뭐하고 있었어?
Thanks. What are we doing?
음악을 모두 듣고 있었어
I'm listening to all these songs
Dorneget이 다운로드한
that Dorneget downloaded.
솔직히 말해서
모든 음악이 별로야
To be honest,
most of them really suck.
그리고 잠시동안
왜 내가 이걸 하고 있지?
And then, for a minute, I'm,
like, Why am I doing this when
누군가는 밖에서 내 친구들과 국립공원을
폭발시키는데? 이런 생각을 했어
somebody's out there blowing up
my friends and national parks
이건 중요한게 아니야
and who knows what else"
But that's not the point.
그럼 요점이 뭐야?
그건 그 리듬이야
So what is the point?
It's the rhythm.
너도 알겠지만
나는 테크노음악을 매우 좋아해
You know, I love a good
techno-industrial beat
as much as your next
범죄수사 다음으로
musically-obsessed
forensic scientist, but
00:24:51,184 -> 00:24:58,252
그냥 들어봐
내가 고음역대와 저음역을 필터 처리를 하면
just listen to what happens
when I filter down the high end
to hear the
rhythm track,
and then roll off
the low end.
00:24:58,522 -> 00:24:58,023
♪ ♪
들려? 이건 매우 정확해
See? It's like it's too precise.
이건 이건..
It's-it's like
it's sending...
모스 부호야
Morse code.
빈 공간에 모스 부호가 있어
There's code imbedded
in these songs.
그래 그건 무언가를 설명하고 있어
Yeah, it's spelling
out something.
베이스 라인에 감춰진 메세지지
It's a message hidden
in a bass line.
수백개가 넘어
And there's hundreds of them.
이게 'Calling'이 아이들과 얘기한 방법이야
This is how The Calling
is talking to these kids.
음악에 관한 것이아니야
It's not about music.
그들은 아이들에게
가서 사람을 해치라고 말하고 있어
They're telling them
to go hurt people.
"여성해군이 죽었다
네가 할 수 있는 것을 증명해라"
McGEE: Navy woman is dead.
Now prove what you can do.
Brad Simek의 컴퓨터에서 얻은
It's a decoded
message we pulled
음악에 있는 메세지입니다
from the music on
Brad Simek's computer.
"네가 할 수 있는 것을 증명해라"
Prove what you can do"
그를 움직이고, 버스를 폭파했어요
Drove him
to blow up the bus.
이것이 음악을 위장한 코드다?
And this is code disguised
as music?
뒤틀어진 거에요
It's actually a warped
백비트의 모스코드와 함께
Morse code with a backbeat.
누가 보낸거야?
Who sent it?
An endless spiral of phony e-mail
방화벽과 TOR protocol에 막힌
가짜 이메일 주소들이
addresses blocked by firewalls
끊이지 않고 있어요.
시작은 누군지 모르구요
and TOR protocols,
origin unknown.
Luke Harris는요 Gibbs?
Luke Harris, Gibbs.
그의 이십대는요?
What's his 20?
그는 아이돌봄이와 우리 집에 있습니다
He's at my house with
an agent and Child Services.
지금 MTAC으로 와요
McGee 너도
MTAC, now.
You, too, McGee.
Girard 장관님
VANCE:
Commissioner Girard,
아시겠지만 Teague 요원입니다
you know
Officer Teague.
아직 기뻐할 만한 것이 없는 것 같은데요
We have not had
the pleasure, no.
당신은 소도 자를 수 있어요
You can cut the
bull, ladies.
00:26:18,342 -> 00:26:21,875
CIA와 and French DGSI가 오래된 친구라는
정보를 얻었습니다
I know for a fact
that CIA
and French DGSI
are old friends.
우리는 한번인가 두번 암호를 해독했죠
JOANNA:
We may have
broken some code once or twice.
00:26:25,581 -> 00:26:29,717
비밀이 터져나왔군요
Well, since the proverbial cat
is out of the bag, Joanna,
Joanna, Ned가 많은 생명을
구한걸 알아줬으면 좋겠어요
I want you to know,
Ned saved my life.
듣고 있습니다 장관님
We're listening,
Commissioner.
얼마전에 예상하지 못한 파일을 가로챘어요
My office recently intercepted
an unexpected file--
'Calling'이 만든 비디오 게임이에요
a videogame
created by The Calling,
무료로 배포되고 있구요
distributed for free.
그 안에 다른 메세지가 있다고 생각하시는 군요
Girard's people think that
there's another
embedded message inside.
00:26:48,371 -> 00:26:50,804
어떤 메세집니까?
저흰 모르겠어요
Well, what kind of message?
GIRARD: We don't know.
그러나 분석가가 말해주길
But my analysts tell me
중요한 것은 단지 게임을 끝날 때
접근할 수 있을꺼라더군요
the key is only accessible
once you finish the game.
그들은 그걸 할 수 없었어요
They have been unable to do so.
전 Ned에게 도움을 구하려고 했어요
I was going to ask Ned for help.
그러나
However,
그가 당신의 게임기술에 대해 말하더군요
Elf Lord.
he spoke very highly
of your gaming skills, Elf Lord.
당신의 도움이 필요해요
We need your help.
와우
McGEE:
Wow.
저희 어머니가 항상 말하셨죠
Well, my mom always said
전 절대 살아있는 비디오 게임을
만들 수 없을거라고 하셨죠
I could never make a living
playing video games.
그래서 McGee가 게임을 끝내면,
어떻게 되는 겁니까?
So, McGee finishes the game,
and then what?
상품은 가장 무서운 것이겠군요
Well, the prize is often
the scariest part of all.
무슨 일이세요?
Can I help you?
안녕하세요
전 Luke의 친구인데요
Yeah, hey.
I'm a friend of Luke's.
그를 데리러 왔어요
I'm here to pick him up.
유감이지만 그건 안되겠는데요
WOMAN:
I'm afraid that's impossible.
Luke는 아무데도 못가요
Luke can't go anywhere.
어떻게 이 주소를 알았죠?
How did you get
this address?
얼마나 걸릴까요?
You ever wonder
how much longer?
뭐가 얼마나 걸려요?
How much longer what?
Well, don't forget how long I've
been in the game, too, Gibbs.
9/11사태 이후,
풍경들은 변화를 간직하기 시작했어요
Post 9/11, the landscape
just keeps changing.
더이상 싸우고 있지 않다고
말하기 힘들었어요
Hard to tell who
we're fighting anymore.
현명한 여성이군
FRANKS:
Bright woman.
내 인생에서 그녀는 어디 있었나?
Where was she
all my life?
내 말은, 우리가 그들을 찾는다면,
그들을 체포할 수 있을꺼에요
I mean, we can keep finding
them, keep arresting them.
사기꾼들은 토끼들처럼 증가하죠
Crooks multiply
like rabbits.
그러나
TEAGUE:
But...
아직도, 우리가 잡으려고 하는 사람이 누구죠?
who are we really
trying to catch
after all these years?
00:28:26,869 -> 00:28:28,902
당신이 잡으려고 하는 사람이 누구죠?
(sighs)
Who are you
trying to catch?
나쁜 놈들
Bad guys.
아직 나쁜놈들을 찾고 있어요
Still looking for the bad guys.
(elevator bell chimes)
Gibbs,
방금 전화걸고 있었어요
I just dialed you.
집에 무슨 일이 생긴것 같아요
Something happened
at your house.
한 소년이 그를 데려갔어요, Gibbs.
A boy took him, Gibbs.
어디로, Paula?
모르겠어요
Where, Paula?
(crying): I don't know.
그는 그냥 가버렸어요
He was just gone.
(Bishop sighs)
보안전문가들은 그들이 오는걸 보지 못했데요
Security detail
never saw it coming.
Ten stitches
to the back of the head.
한 명 이상이 있었나?
There more than one of them?
아마도요
Maybe.
Paula...
그 아이는 15살정도였나요?
was this kid fifteenish,
키가 크고, 아마 중동아이 였죠?
tall, maybe Middle Eastern?
저희가 캠퍼스에서 본 소년 같아요
Sounds like the boy
we saw on campus.
계속해
Go ahead, say it.
필요 없어
No need.
(phone chimes)
(knocking on door)
흠
VANCE:
Mm-hmm.
국장님
Director.
들어오게
Come on in.
당신이 스카치를 좋아하길 바래요
I hope you like Scotch.
오늘은 그럴게요
좋군요
Oh! Tonight I do.
Good.
당신은 내 다른 삶에 대해 읽고 있군요
Oh. I see you've been reading up
on my other life.
당신의 보스가 내게 주었어요
Yeah, your bosses read me in
on just how close
당신과 CIA가 어떻게 10대들을 포섭하는지
you and the CIA are to this
world of recruiting teens.
우린 가깝지 않아요
Oh, we're not close.
우린 함께 있죠
We're in.
비밀리에 'Calling'에 관계된
일을 하는 동안
Months of undercover
work on The Calling.
그들은 당신이 이 정보를 쏟아낼까봐
두려워 했어요
They're afraid you're about
to flush it all down the drain.
그걸 이용할까봐요?
By using it?
아뇨 단지 NCIS의 조사를 도와
00:30:09,505 -> 00:30:11,939
자신들이 위태롭게 되는 것을요
No, by jeopardizing your cover
to help
with an NCIS investigation.
난 내 아들을 죽인 사람을 찾아 낼 수 있어요
Look, I can find the people
who killed my son,
그리고 다른 사람이 죽는 걸 막을꺼에요
and prevent the death
of God knows how many others.
국장님, CIA는 지금 Sadiq가
어디에 있는지 아는것 같습니다
Director, the CIA now thinks
they know where Sadiq is.
그래서 당신은 내가
그들의 요구를 무시하길 바라는건가요?
So, you want me to
disregard their request,
look the other way?
00:30:26,322 -> 00:30:30,090
당신은 확실하게 하기 위해
저를 여기로 부르셨죠
You called me up here
to make it clear
00:30:32,328 -> 00:30:35,662
무슨일이 있어도 NCIS가 승인받지 않은 위험을
that under no circumstances
would NCIS take
any unauthorized risk
현재 진행중인 CIA 작전에 넘겨서는 안되요
to a CIA operation
currently in progress.
미션은 달성하고
Mission accomplished.
그리고 국장님은 끝내는 거죠
Now you have an out.
그 가정상은
나는 당신편이군요
Well, that's assuming
I'm on your side.
음
Mm.
만약 그게 아니라면
Well, if you're not,
when I leave,
내가 떠날때, 내 보스에게 나에대해 고자질 해요
you can call my boss
and tattle on me.
우리는 오랫동안 서로 이해해왔으니까요
Long as we understand
each other.
그러나 만약 당신이 전화를 한다면
But if you make that call...
남는건 아무것도 없을거에요
(clears her throat)
...we gain nothing.
Sadiq도 Luke도
No Sadiq, no Luke.
Ned이 죽음은 헛되이 남아있겠죠
Ned's death remains in vain.
전 제 선택을 한겁니다
I've made my choice.
안녕히 계세요
Good night.
(keypad beeping)
(phone line ringing)
어떻게 우리가 여기에 있을 수 있지 Ned?
GIBBS:
How did we get here, Ned?
테러리스트들은 아이들을 이용해
Terrorists using kids.
그들의 부모들이 옆 방에 있을때
Talking to them
in their bedrooms at night
그들의 침실에서 그들에게 얘기해
while their parents
are in the room next door.
이리 오렴 신참
Come on, Gunny.
아이들은 수세기 동안 전쟁과 싸워 왔단다
Kids have been fighting
wars for centuries.
세계대전, 종교 전쟁
World wars, religious wars.
우리는 우리의 자아가 한 실수를 바로잡으며
젊은 시기를 보내왔지
We send in the young to fix
our ego-driven mistakes.
왜 여기에 있어요?
Why are you here?
왜?
Why?
심각해요, Mike
Seriously, Mike.
왜?
Why?
왜 당신과 Kate and Pacci, Jenny가 비행기 옆에 서 있었죠?
Why did I see you
and Kate and Pacci,
Jenny out by the plane?
00:32:12,061 -> 00:32:14,561
네?
Huh?
뭘 원하는 거에요?
What do you want?
너는 뭘 원하나?
사람들은 너를 믿고 있어
People count on you.
항상
Always have.
난 절대 그것을 물어본게 아니에요
I never asked for that.
네가 잃어버린 모든 사람들을 위해,
얼마나 많은 사람들을 구했지?
For every one you've lost,
how many have you saved?
난 충분히 구하지 못했어요
I haven't saved enough.
스스로는?
What about yourself?
누가 자넬 구하나?
Who's gonna save you?
(whistling)
(train horn blowing
in distance)
(kettle whistling subsides)
(train passing by)
(crossing bell clanging
in distance)
Gibbs.
그들이 Luke를 어디로 데려갔는지 알아냈어요
I know where they took Luke.
(banging on door)
(pounding on door)
들어오실래요?
Want to come in?
(gasping, shuddering)
몇번이나 Vance가 당신에게 말했어요?
How much did Vance tell you?
충분히
Enough.
Sadiq를 찾기위해 CIA 정보를 이용했죠
I used CIA Intel to find Sadiq.
당신은 정보를 이용했지, 당신을 위해서
우리를 위해서가 아니라
You used the Intel...
for you, not us.
이건 공동 작전이에요
This is a joint operation.
아니, 이건 우리 작전이지
No, it's not.
This is our case.
이 자가 아이들을 모집했어요
그는 폭탄을 만들었구요
This man recruits children.
He builds bombs
그리고 당신은 그가 Luke의 부모를
죽이는 것을 봤어요
And you watched him kill Luke's
parents in cold blood.
명백히 하기위해서
I'll make one thing
perfectly clear:
난 CIA는 신경 안써
I don't care about the CIA.
난 단지 내가 잃어버린 요원을 신경쓸 뿐이지
I care about the agent I lost.
여기에 있고 싶으면,
우리 방식으로 행동해
You want to be in on this,
you do it our way.
난 그것을 위태롭게 했어요
I jeopardized it.
그는 어디있어?
Where is he?
Zakho.
왜 연방정부의 보호아래 있는 아이들을 데려갔지?
Why grab a kid under
federal custody?
왜냐하면
Because...
그는 보호중이니까요
he was in custody.
그는 우리의 이름, 장소 모든것을 알고 있어
He's seen us.
Names, locations,
모든 것을
All of it.
우리가 타겟이야
We're targets.
그들은 그를 통해 정보를 얻어낼 거에요
They will get
the information out of him.
당신이 할 수 있는 것은 아무것도 없어
And there is nothing
you can do about it.
(train horn blowing
in distance)
(ringing)
Timothy McGee 요원입니다
Special Agent Timothy McGee.
McGee!
보스 죄송해요
Boss, hey, uh, sorry,
Abby와 비디오 게임과 관련된 일을 하고 있었어요
I was with Abby working
on the video game and...
Daniel Budd?
(Gibbs speaking indistinctly)
네 전 여기 있어요
Yeah.
Uh, yeah, I'm on it.
어디세요?
Where are you?
우리는 Samar와 출발하는 중이야
We're on our way
with Samar.
Samar요?
어떻게 어떻게
With Samar?
How did-How did you...
(hangs up)
Gibbs?
Gibbs와 Joanna 출발했데요
He and Joanna
are on their way up.
그들은 단지 Sadiq Samar를 예약했어
They just booked Sadiq Samar.
어떻게 Sadiq을 찾았지?
How'd they find Sadiq?
Daniel Budd는 누구에요?
And who's Daniel Budd?
'Calling' 의 리더
The leader
of The Calling.
Daniel Budd.
25살이고, 영국인이네요
25 years old, British
정치적 운동가이면서
테러리스트의 리더를 맡고 있죠
political activist and
underground terrorist leader.
Budd는 런던에서 DJ로 시작했어요
Budd started as a London DJ.
그럼 음악에 관한 건 설명이 되네요
McGEE:
That would explain the music.
그의 짧은 전성기 이후
So after
his 15 minutes
of fame were over,
00:35:43,579 -> 00:35:45,245
그는 필사적으로 남아있길 원했어요
he desperately wanted
to stay relevant.
잘못된 유년기로 방황했고
Surrounded himself
with misguided youth.
강도짓을 시작했어요
Started robbing
from their parents.
하찬은 절도는 그를
절도와 납치로 이끌었어요
Petty theft led to assault
and kidnapping.
그는 테러리즘에서 충격적인 타당성을 발견했어요
He found disturbing
relevance in terrorism.
제 NSA에 정보에 의하면
My NSA informant
just I.D.'d Luke
Luke가 Zakho교외로 향하고 있네요
somewhere on
the outskirts of Zakho.
그는 이미 거기 있어요
He's already there.
우리가 BOLO를 가기 전에
이미 전용기는 이륙했어요
BISHOP:
Private charter took off
before we got the BOLO out.
00:36:01,897 -> 00:36:03,263
거리를 주시할까요 보스?
Eyes on the street, boss?
아냐 우리와 시작하지
DiNozzo, 가방챙겨
No, start with ours.
DiNozzo, grab your go bag.
Teague요원이 수송일정을 잡을꺼야
Officer Teague
is gonna arrange transport.
비행기는 한시간 내에 떠난다
Plane leaves in an hour.
이것이 Sadiq가 말한 이웃이에요
TEAGUE: This is the neighborhood
that Sadiq described.
내 정보원들이 밴에서
My people saw a van
아이들이 그룹으로 내리는 것을
unload a group of Westernized
teens close by.
그들은 차로 이동되고 있어요
Then they were
transferred into cars
다양한 장소로요
and taken to
various locations.
세시네요
Three o'clock.
저기를 보세요
밝고, 반짝이는 신발이에요
Look at the bright,
shiny kicks.
나는 그녀가 그 팀과 있다고 생각해요
Mm. I doubt she's here
with the debate team.
그녀를 따라가
Follow her.
Sadiq Samar.
결국은
Finally.
얘기하는 것이 가치가 있고
Someone worth talking to.
우리가 전에 만난 적 있나?
Have we met before?
전혀요
Never.
그러나 난 당신이 누군지 알고 있죠 국장님
But I know
who you are, Director.
그리고 전 우리가 둘다 똑똑한 사람들이라는 걸 알고 있어요
And I know that
we're both intelligent men.
난 자랑스러워요
And I am confident
우리는 상호간의
무엇을 얻을 수 있을 거에요
that we can come
to some sort of mutual...
이해하세요?
understanding?
협상을 얘기하는군
You mean negotiate.
협상은 우리가 교착상태라는 것을 제안하죠
Negotiation suggests
that we're at an impasse.
너는 테러리스트야
You're a terrorist.
우리는 교착상태고
We're at an impasse.
심문자로서의 당신의 평판은
당신을 앞서죠
Your reputation as
an interrogator precedes you.
오 이런 Sadiq
Oh, hell, Sadiq...
난 지금 시작하려고 하네
I am just getting started.
그들이 손지갑만한 크기에 들어오나요?
Do they come in wallet size?
그게 재밌다고 생각하나?
You think that's funny?
제가 생각하기엔 당신은 자발적으로
시간을 낭비하는 것 같은데요
I think that you are wasting
your valuable time.
00:38:18,200 -> 00:38:22,803
Matthew Rousseau는 이미 감옥에 가는 중이야
Matthew Rousseau is already
halfway to a supermax prison.
내게 Daniel Budd를 넘겨
Give me Daniel Budd.
당신은 절대 그를 찾지 못할꺼에요
You will never find him.
우리는 둘다 현명한 사람들이지
We're both intelligent men.
나를 시험해봐
Try me.
이집트의 야외 레스토랑
The outdoor restaurant in Egypt.
그랜드 캐년
The Grand Canyon.
큰 야외장소
Big outdoor spaces.
만약 그 폭발물들이 테스트였다면
If these bombings
were tests...
다음 타겟은 누가될까?
...what's your next target?
다른사람들 중에?
Among others?
흠.
Mm-hmm.
나이들고 완고한 남자지
Old, stubborn men
벤치에 앉아
sit on benches
their entire lives
삶과 그들의 방식을 설정하죠
and get set
in their ways.
나이, 국장
Age, Director...
나이는 계몽된 젊음의 적이죠
age is the enemy
of enlightened youth.
00:39:33,842 -> 00:39:36,677
쪼개져 이쪽은 내가 맡을께
Split off. I got this.
(rooster crows in distance)
용을 따라가 McGee
잠시만
ABBY: Follow the dragon, McGee.
BISHOP: Wait.
그건 용에 관한게 아니에요
그건 검에 관한거에요
It's not about the dragon,
it's about the sword.
그걸 고블린에게 써요
Use it on
the goblin.
둘다 틀렸어
그건 물약에 관한거야
You're both wrong.
It's about the potions.
노란것을 집어
Mmm, pick the yellow one.
아냐 노란색은 히어로가 아니야
보라색이야
No, the yellow one's not
the hero one, the purple is.
깼다
Got it.
깼구나 내 Elf Lord!
You win, my Elf Lord!
내 감각이 죽지 않았다는 것을 느끼기에 좋았어
Nice to know
I haven't lost my touch.
이제 뭐가 일어나지?
Now what happens?
음 드래곤의 왕의 왕관도 썼고
Well, besides being crowned
the King of Darrigone...
00:40:04,607 -> 00:40:06,139
잠시만 이건 뭐죠?
Wait. What's this?
Abby 방화벽이 가동됐어, 맞지?
Abby, the firewalls
are up, right?
맞아, 다음 단계과 회로레벨 게이트웨이야
Yeah, next generation
and circuit-level gateway.
격자무늬야
BISHOP:
They're grids.
여행 목적지
비즈니스 중심지
Travel destinations.
Business hubs.
해군기지
Naval bases.
'Calling'의 다음 타겟들이야
Places for The Calling
to target next.
어떻게 그들이 이 모든것에 접근할 수 있었지?
How did they get access
to all this?
그들은 내부의 아이들을 데리고 있어요
They have kids inside.
정부관계자들의 아이요
Children of
government employees.
Luke가 여전히 그들과 있으면 어쩌죠?
What if Luke's
still with them?
그들을 깁스의 집으로 데려가면 어쩌죠?
What if he steered them
to Gibbs's house?
McGee!
국장님 이것 좀 보세요
Director, you gotta see this.
지금은 아니야 McGee.
Not now, McGee.
대법관들, 정확히 그들이 어딨지?
The supreme court justices--
exactly where are they?
그들은 후퇴중이에요
뉴스에 나왔어요
They're on retreat.
It's all over the news.
나도 그건 알아
I know that.
그들이 어디있는 거지?
I asked where?
애팔래치아 산맥의 건물에 있어요
A compound in the Appalachians.
지금 당장 그들을 제재해 당장!
Well, get it on lockdown. Now.
무엇을 원하죠?
What do you want?
미연방 요원이다
United States federal agent.
넌 여기 있으면 안돼
여긴 안전하지 않아
You can't be here.
It's not safe.
난 산책나왔을 뿐이에요
I'm out for a walk.
그것이 그들이 말한 할일이에요
That's what they told me to do.
그들? 누가 네게 말했지?
Who? Who told you that?
제 새 친구들이요
My new friends.
내가 믿는 사람들
The people I trust.
(phone ringing)
DiNozzo입니다
DiNozzo.
이라크에 온걸 환영한다
DiNozzo 요원
Welcome to Iraq, Agent DiNozzo.
누구시죠?
Who is this?
난 당신에 관한 것을 아주 많이 읽었어
I've been reading
about you a lot.
그것은 엄청나서
It's fabulous to finally
결국은 내가 너와 알고있는 것 처럼 만들더군
make myself acquainted with you.
Daniel인가요?
This is Daniel?
나는 많은 사람들에게 많은 것들 이지 (?)
I am many things to many people.
내게 당신은 테러리스트에요
Well, to me you're a terrorist.
불행한 이름 "테러리스트"
Such an unfortunate moniker,
that: terrorist.
전 진짜 가봐야겠어요
I really need to go.
안돼 넌 우리와 함께 갈꺼야
No, you're coming with us.
전 그렇게 생각하지 않는데요
I don't think so.
우리는 소년을 원해
넌 무엇을 원하나?
We want the boy.
What do you want?
그냥 들어지는것.
Just to be heard.
존경을 받으며
To be respected.
깨진 약속이 건네지는 것이 아니라
Not to be handed
your broken promises.
세대차이에 오신 것을 환영합니다
Welcome to the generation gap.
오래된 습관, 힘들게 죽는 것, Daniel.
Old habits die hard, Daniel.
혹은 그들이 그냥 죽거나
Or they just die.
오 안돼 안돼
배고프세요?
No, no, no, no, no, no...
Are you hungry?
당신은 배고파요
You are hungry,
you are hungry.
Luke 라는 그 소년
The boy, Luke...
내가 나쁜 소식을 전하게 되어 유감이네
I'm sorry for being
the bearer of bad news,
그러나 이것들은 그들이 나타나는 것보다
항상 더 복잡하지
but these things are always more
complicated than they appear.
Gibbs 요원이 상당히 실망할꺼야
Agent Gibbs will be
so disappointed.
Gibbs?
LUKE:
Agent Gibbs?
그러나 우린 반드시 기억해야해
DANIEL:
But we must remember,
그들은 겨우 아이들이라는 것을
they're only children.
(people screaming)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Mimmi's 1st substitle
@elder_man